Next Episode
Next episode
Well, nice to meet you all on the Sakura High School Channel!
Well, it's just Buddy's!
Good morning, hello, good evening.
Well, let's see... I've been invited as a...
I've been invited to be a guest collaborator.
I don't care what I sound like or what I look like.
I can't start without my thumbs!
I'm already taking pictures for the camera, you three!
Come on!
I can't do this anymore! I can't do this alone! I can't start without you!
And Ten Yamazaki, who is in the front of the group, is always telling them not to go. I've seen how much he likes that kind of bad behavior.
Hello, hello, hello!
You have to come quickly.
And you guys were so funny. You were so cute.
I'm gonna set the camera down for a second.
I think I heard someone stop. Oh, that was me. Was that the camera outside? That's me. Is that an outside camera?
No, of course not. Everyone wants to see it.
Okay, it's set.
Couldn't you close the distance a little bit? You're not very good at this.
You're used to it. No, I'm just a beginner YouTuber.
I'm just a beginner YouTuber. I'm just getting started.
What's wrong with Karin?
What's wrong? It's not good. It's a radio show.
Shall we get started? What's taking so long?
I didn't introduce myself. Are you ready, Pen?
Yes, I'm fine. Yes, I'm fine.
Well, okay. You don't have to do it like that, but it's a very important one.
I can see it, can't I? Okay? Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Oh, why did you just say that? Uh-oh. Laughing.
Yoshi's doing it. Yoshi's doing it now.
Yoshi from Mario Kart, he sounds like that.
It's not Yoshi.You're not Josie, are you?
Well, I haven't finished introducing myself yet, so...
May I ask you to face the camera and introduce yourself while you're still awake?
Yes, I'm Honoh Tamura of Sakurazaka 46. Pleased to meet you.
Hanae.
I'm Karin Fujii. Nice to meet you.
Hanane-chan.
I'm Ten Yamazaki. Nice to meet you.
Have you ever seen the Sakurazaka Channel?
You cook. Oh, thank you! I did!
The one where you cook for Hanane.
Yes, that's right. In the opening, Honno said...
Um, Honno-chan said in the opening that she would cook for a certain member today.
A few seconds before that, she was on the show.
That's right.
This is probably Kabayashi-chan! I said, "I'm sure that's her!
That's what was written on the thumbnail.
That's the thumbnail.
But do you take pictures of this often?
Do you feel like you've said so? I haven't yet.
You haven't? I haven't either.
Well, we're shooting individually now.
It's quite rare to do it with this many people.
Oh, rare.
We all work individually.
I often shoot by myself.
At most, there are two of us.
Did Hanae-chan say she wanted to cook by herself?
Yes, I've got a few ideas.
So you're thinking of doing something on your own in the future, too.
What?
You mean there's a possibility it could go up.
There's a possibility of going up.
Suddenly it's a low step.
But I haven't decided yet.
What do you want to do?Do you have any ideas about what you want to do?
Uh, please don't tell me.
Okay, okay.
I'm sorry.
I didn't let you know.
We've all come up with a list of things we'd like to do.
We'll be able to choose from among them.
That's what everyone wants to do.
Who wants to go to the Anpanman Museum?
Suddenly, we're looking for people.
Everyone?
I'd like to go.
In the Sagaradaka Channel?
That's right.
I'd like to go.
I was wondering if anyone wanted to go.
I asked.
I couldn't get anyone to go.
I don't think they'd be interested.
It sounds like fun.
I'd like to go, wouldn't you?
Great, don't do something you're not interested in.
No, no, no.
Just normal.
Like, "It would be nice if it was normal.
Even if I don't say much, I say it.
I don't say flattering things.
That's great.
It sounds like fun.
I don't want to say that.
You seem like you're having a good time.
Thank you.
What about you, Kon?
What are you going to do?
What I want to do.
I've already told you.I'm just saying.
Maybe I have too many orders.
I don't know if it's because I'm too particular, or if it's because I don't want to make too much progress on the project.
But I've been told that I'm happier
I'm glad to hear that.
What's that?
Well then...
What's that gesture?
What is that, a turrico?
But...
The base is simple.
But the base is very simple, and you are very particular about the situation
I think it's great.
It's good.
You look kind of bashful, are you okay?
What do you want to see?
You're right.
I'm curious about what you want to see.
Mr. Toyama.
Me?
Of course.
What do you want to see?
One by one, please.
Sure thing!
What do you want to see?
Plus up to three.
That's great.
What do you want to see?
Nothing?
That's sad.
No.
He likes us so much.
I think I'll start with Tenchan.
About a year ago...
I still think of Ten-chan...I knew it! I knew it! I knew it! I knew it! I knew it! I knew it!
I miss her.
Don't you have that look on your face?
What's wrong with your face?
It's High Speed Tencho.
Tenchan was great in the commercials.
Can we do a YouTube project?
A YouTube project.
So, for example, 30 minutes of endurance high-speed Tenchan.
I might want to do it.
I know, right?
It would be nice.
We could come up with a lot of poses and stuff.
I'm pretty sure that's a selfie, right?
That's right.
For 30 minutes.
If you strike the same pose, you have to start over.
We're off to a bad start.
It's a fall show, right?
So we're going to make a lot of faces and expressions.
And do it at high speed.
How's that?
And then we'll do medium and low speed.
We'll do them too.
Wait, medium speed is the worst.
Why is low speed the hardest?
I don't like low speed.
I'll take care of the low speed, please.
But they're always saying "slow speed, Tenchan!
But I immediately say, "Low speed, Tenchan!
That's great.
But if it's a medium speed...
Normal?
Normal.
No fun?
No.Yeah.
So medium speed is not the best.
I'll have the three of you play a game.
A game?
We can all choose together.
Whoever wins gets to choose the fastest speed.
Oh, I see.
I think I'll stop.
Would you look at that?
I think I'll quit.
But will you come on again, Sakurazaka Channel?
Who is it?
Please.
Me?
I think this radio style
I think it's very interesting.
Are you going to get out of the radio booth?
I'm with Mr. Toyama.
I think I live in the booth.
I have other jobs, so...
Maybe we don't know each other that well.
No, no, no.
I'd stay here if I wanted to.
And you three come back here again.
I'd like the three of you to come back here and do something with Buddy's people.
I'd be happy to make a deal with them if you'll have me.
I'd like to do that.
That's what I'm thinking.
Plus something?
Plus?
Something that directly helps Buddy's.
Let's do it.
That's a really good idea.
I'm totally up for it.
Grab a mike.
I want to go, too.I want to go, too.
He says you're busy.
I'm totally fine.
Can you go?
I'm busy, but I'll do my best.
Don't say that.
I'm busy.
Then I'll go.
I'll go with the photographer and the guys.
I'll go with Sue and Jane.
Let's go.
Listen to what they have to say.
I'll take you there, for example.
The three of us.
And then we'll call each other again.
Surprise me.
That's so cool.
To Buddy's.
I'd like to get married.
I want to go.
Then we'll continue that on the Sakura Sagi Channel.
Maybe we'll do it.
Maybe we'll do it on location.
What about you, Karin?
Yes?
Is this the broadcast?
Is that what this is about?
What is it?
Last week?
We met last week.
I'm doing a show on locatem.
School of Log Education Committee.
I'm on the show.
You've met Honachan before, right?
We met on the radio.I've met you on the radio.
Ten-chan, you know, she commented a lot.
You commented on my show a lot.
I haven't been able to get out for a long time.
Hello?
Are you awake?
Are you still sleeping?
I'm awake.
You're awake.
This is not a real hearing test.
I'll tell him myself.
You shouldn't say so much.
So Karin came to see me.
Just the two of us.
About the song "Start Over" from the 6th single
about the song "Start Over," the sixth single.
We talked a lot about it.
Thank you very much.
Why are you laughing?
I thought there was something going on here.
What's going on here?
I don't know.
Oh, it's okay.
It's just... it's just... it's just... it's just so...
I saw your fangs.
No, no, but...
Then I'll come closer.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
But I don't know.
I'm not sure I've ever been with you before.
With me?
Like with Karin.
I don't know...
I don't really feel like I'm close to him.
I thought we were good friends.I thought they were kind of close.
I'll be watching.
Really?
What do you think, Karin?
I don't think so.
Kasuka...
So faint.
Yes, well...
As for me, well...
I like Sakurazaka too.
Thank you very much
I've got a lot on my mind.
A place where I can express my feelings...
I'm so grateful that we met today.
I'm very grateful.
But today...
About 5 minutes before the show started
About five minutes before the show starts.
I had to wait outside the studio for a while.
At first you say, "Thank you very much.
"Good morning," or something like that.
Karin-chan was standing next to me
She looks at me and says
How do you feel now?
Scared.
Of course you're scared.
All of a sudden?
Scared.
What was that about?
You seem more fidgety than usual.
I was wondering how you were feeling.
I was curious.
From now on.
A man suddenly appeared on the Sakurazaka Channel.
I wonder how she feels about that.
He's not just a man.I'm not just a man.
Give me a description of what kind of man you are.
I'm not just any man.
What kind of man are you?
I'm not just a man.
You're right.
Since the time of Zelkova...
I've always been
Enthusiastically
Mr. Toyama was the only one who could draw out our charms and talk about them.
I'll really give you 1,000 yen later.
I don't want it. Don't you want it?
Why don't you want it?
I have 1,000 yen.
You have it?
Yes, I have it.
You seem like the type who only has coins.
Maybe a lot of coins.
I'll take it then.
Why are you taking all that?
Do you have 1,000 yen in change?
No, I don't. Bullshit.
Do you have 1,000 yen, pennies?
I don't.
Then, as we go through the day...
I'll give you some more change.
Yay!
I don't know about money.
Okay, sure.
You want something else?
Sure, something else.
What's her charm?
Tell me.
It's a long story.
And I'm still blushing.
She looks amazing.Looks amazing.
Okay, one at a time.
When the time comes...
I just couldn't help but notice...
I don't like money.
As both Kosen-chan and Ten-chan said...
Ono-chan's just happy.
That's the only thing that bothered me.
Because it's not likely to happen.
That's for sure.
No one will ever know.
Money is a terrible thing to hold a grudge against.
And food.
Well, today...
Well, it's finally started.
It's starting.
What do you think this is about?
It's not a game.
It's a worldwide broadcast.
That's right.
Yoo-hoo!
Be aware of the camera.
I'm watching you.
Can I say something, Kanin-chan?
Hello.
You heard me.
Let's work hard.
Let's talk.
So, last time...
Kanin-chan came to my radio show.
I knew we had an hour to air.
I just didn't have enough time.
And a song.
It took one song to start over.
And the coupling song.
It was really cool.It's so cool.
Some of the songs are cute.
Some songs have a totally different vibe than the start overs.
I couldn't really talk about them.
It would be great if you could make a place like that.
I'd be happy if you could make such a place for us.
I was saying on the microphone...
Sakurazaka's manager
He's very good, isn't he?
Mr. Moneyasan, right?
Mr. Saito of A&R immediately moved in
And with this stick
Adaasu!
Amazing butt
Oh, my ass!
Ya!
I wasn't picked up by 3 in Tokyo and lived for 4 years. I live in Sapporo, Hokkaido.
I'm from Sapporo, Hokkaido
I'll try to make it so... no, you'll be fine
I'm glad you're having fun with me!
I'm glad you pointed that at me!
You'll be fine, girl
Okay, then...
I'm just saying that to Penn-chan, so it's both okay.
I'm an idol... so you said it might not flow... but it will.
I'll be fine.
And she's been on a lot of singing TV shows and radio shows.
I've also had a lot of radio appearances, variety show stems, and magazine interviews.
I've had many opportunities to see you in interviews with magazines and so on.
I've already said all I can say, so please don't ask me again.
I've said all I can say, so please don't ask me.
I've had a chance to talk about the start-over, but I'm not sure if I can explain the song or not.
I've been thinking that it's very difficult to explain a song, and it's been like that for a long time.
I think I've been a little bit reserved in what I say. I want to explain the song and say, "This is the song.
I want you to listen, but I feel like I'm becoming more and more afraid to do so.I want you to do it, but I feel like I'm getting more and more scared of it, and I think I'm becoming more and more critical of it.
I don't know why, but maybe it's because I'm learning more and more about the song.
But of course I want to leave it to the person who is listening to it, but I think it's very difficult to verbalize my feelings.
I think it's very difficult to verbalize my feelings, but I think I'm good at it.
I really want to convey my feelings, but I don't know if I want to convey them accurately or not.
I don't want to convey it in a bad way, or in a different way, or in a bad way.
I'm starting to think that there are a lot of interpretations, and I don't want it to come across that way.
The manager was nodding his head the whole time, but I have the same feelings.
I'm not the same type of person.
I'm not the same type of person, so when I'm interviewed together with members, all I get is, "Wow, I didn't know you had that kind of thing.
So it's hard for me to talk about it.
Especially since Sakurazaka became a member, each person's way of thinking and expressing themselves has become so much more alive.
In a sense, we're all heading in the same direction, but I don't know what to say about our thoughts and feelings toward the songs.
In a sense, we're all heading in the same direction, but we all have our own thoughts and feelings about the songs.
I may have mentioned this to Karin before, but before the last chorus... she comes from the back, judging the middle of the song, and we all unite as one...
I think that you can't do that if you don't have the same feeling.
Even though we have different ideas, we are looking at the same place, so I think that's why we can be so moved.
That's why I think it's great that we don't talk about it.
I think it's good that we don't talk about it, or that we don't become shy when we do.
So when we talk, we don't get shy, and I think each one of us is different.
I think it's like, "Well, I'm not good at speaking up, but I'm not good at talking.
The encore of the 8th and final show of the third tour in Osaka was suddenly and unexpectedly triggered without any warning, and I was able to watch it on the live stream.
And I was so impressed that I was able to watch it on TV... and the encore was over.
And then Kira-chan and Hono-chan, who was standing next to me, were really impressed by what Kani said, and I think it was one of her best business cards.
And then after Karin said "thank you" and bowed, and then Hono-chan hugged her, and I think it was on a picture.
That's so embarrassing.
I don't want that to be in the picture.
I didn't mean for that to happen.
Can I ask if you did? But it must've been really, really great to show off what we'd all been working on together.
We were all very nervous to perform it, and we also felt that Buddies was expecting a lot from this single.
I guess that's why we had to preserve the moment of the first performance.So now that I'm single, I feel that everyone is supporting me.
I feel that everyone supports me now that I'm single, and Honoha is always close to me.
I feel like she's more like a big sister.
I feel like I can always count on you. I feel like you're always close to me.
This single also has a copy of the next one, right?
Yes, it is.
Start Over is a great song.
We all support each other.
Don't take it alone.
Mentally.
Performance-wise
It's not going to happen.
All of us.
I'm glad that all the first-term students and second-term students
I'm so glad we have all of you, first-term students and second-term students.
You're moving so well, aren't you, DancePracticePlatics and Platics and Platics and Platics?
That's "Dumpla-Platics" and "Platics.
Oh, well, you're just being cool.
I mean, those moves, they're... they're... they're... they're just so...
I want to see it.
Like this move here.
It's amazing.
You don't see much of that on TV, do you?
That's right.
I can't believe she's doing that.
It's like a cute move all of a sudden, right? That's right, that's right.
That's great, too.
It's not a consideration, but it's a part of the work.
It's like we Buddies are able to feel even the parts we can't see.
We buddies, you know...
I was thinking about how cute the drone is when it's circling...
What's going on with the cuteness of the drone while it's circling?
Thank you very much. Oto-chan is at the center.
The music video is really different from the rest of the show. Yes, it was. It was amazing, wasn't it?
The director of the music video explained the atmosphere of the music video and it was really different. It was very different from the materials.
Everyone was really looking forward to seeing what kind of music video it would be. Everyone was really looking forward to it.I wonder what kind of music video everyone is all about. I was really looking forward to it.
So, what was the direction of the music video? The main theme of the music video is that each person has his/her own ability and that a typhoon is coming.
Each one of us has the ability. Anyway. I didn't really understand what was going on.
I don't know... let's see...
I don't know what Karin-chan's name is, but can she turn back time? I can turn back time. Right, at the railroad crossing. Yes, that's right.
And Ten-chan is like a boxer. That's true. I was wondering about that. You're not a boxer? Yes, that's what my fans said.
Like, "Is this what Tenchan is capable of? Like, "Oh, but isn't that it? But isn't that it? You planted the seeds of water fruits, right?
Psychedelic? Psychedelic? Psychedelic? Psychedelic, I guess, is a genre of music.
I see. It sounds fantastic.
Psychokinesis. Yes, psychokinesis, that's it. Wow.
Oh, so this is different. Yes, I'm planting the seeds of water fruits.
That's the kind of character I am, I guess. I'm really serious, just fighting an invisible enemy.
I'm just fighting against an invisible enemy. Yes, during summer vacation at my grandmother's house, I was just fighting inside the house, but I hadn't gone outside yet.
But she looked pretty good, didn't she? That punch. Yes, Takahiro gave me great instructions. She was really fighting, with her mouth agape, saying "sh-sh-sh-sh-sh" as she did it.
I would be more than happy if it became an uplifting song. Yes, it would be.
My face is hidden. It's okay, my face. You're so sweet. You're so kind. Your hand is kind, too. Thank you so much.
Also, a lot of fans who want to see it. I don't have any. Suddenly. Suddenly, it's amazing. No, of course not. Your original tone was terrible.
Was it dangerous? It was dangerous. The tone of your voice. Combinator.
I've never heard of a "2-note" song before.
It's the first time I've ever heard a live song... and I've been asking for it and asking for it.
No one's coming through... who's coming through? The Director of the World Bureau... what was his reaction?
What's the reaction of the World Director?
I'm just getting started... with the long-awaited combiner.
The manager's going to take care of the combinatore... the combinatore... the combinatore... but it's going to be about that dance...
The combination was a song from the production, a song from the Nissho students, and a song from the 3rd year students... each with a different color, but the combination was... well...
I was surprised at how much we danced.
I thought the songs would be more cheerful and fun since it was the middle of the day, but it was pretty much the middle of the night.
But it was pretty good... a little bit too much fun at night.
Like this.
Like this at night.
Kaji-Kaji-Kaji-Kaji-Kaji-Kaji-Kaji-Kajo.
It's more of a romantic song than a happy one.
We'll drive there, and we'll have a car... not like a normal car, but like a vintage car.
It's a cool, stylish song.
I'm not saying much.
And it's also a song about love.And, well, it's a love song, too, I guess.
How about you, Karin? How about this song, "Harbor"?
I loved dancing to it.
I know, right?
I loved it. I loved dancing to it.
And the girl in the center...
I don't know, I haven't seen her yet.
I'm not going to tell you, but I was excited from the moment they told me the center would be this girl.
I know, but I've been excited ever since they announced her as the center.
That's a difficult feeling for you, Karin, but it was unexpected?
I wanted to see it.
I've always wished she had a song in the middle, so it's great that we get to see it this time.
I was looking forward to seeing it as a viewer.
You mean for this song?
Yes, I don't think she's the kind of girl who pops up when it comes to Arthur.
I thought of the combiner and the industrial area and that kind of thing.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but it's a good idea.
Let's get ready to go.
I'm looking forward to this one, too.
I knew about this group, Sakurazaka 46.
Three members of the group are here today.
That's why we're so impressed. I'll say it in all its glory.
Yes, you're right! We're buddies!
Hey!
Let me keep cheering for you!
Look out!
Who said we're in danger?
The cheerleaders are here.
Whisper, "Hang in there.
"Go, go, go, go!
Wow, that's a great sound.
Oh, my God, some kid just walked in.
Oh, no.
It's an innocent kid in short sleeves and shorts.
Boo-bah-shh, good morning, good morning.Good morning.
I just woke up... and I'd like to say hello to you... and thank you... and I'll keep you posted... but so far, so good.
160 points... 160 points... 160 points... 160 points... 160 points... 160 points... 160 points...
160 points in the "nonsense" category... and there's more to come.
Okay, then.
I'm going to ask you to say this... the next title... and I want you to make it loud and clear... for the camera... and I'm going to introduce this one that we've been looking for from our buddies.
I'd like to introduce you to something we've been looking for from our "buddies.
What I want to redo... what do you think?
I'm going to introduce the one thing that you asked for from the "buddies"...
I'm just saying, I'd like to redo it...
Isn't this how it's going to be?
That's great!
Yes, I think it's like that.
Sakurazaka's 466th single is off to a great start!
To commemorate the release of the single, the buddies have asked me what I want to redo!
If you translate "start over," it means to start over.
That's what it means.
I asked for messages about things you want to redo.
I heard that we received a tremendous number of them.
I heard that.
I'm going to call the Buddies who sent me those messages.
I'm going to call them directly and ask them about what they want to redo.
We're going to talk to them about what they want to redo.
Yay!
Um... Miguri...
I don't know... it's a meat-and-greet with a woman... but... it's like a power surge...
I wonder if there will be a handshake at the Osaka Expo with a sense of hydraulic power.
I don't know.
I don't even know what that sense of power is.
I'm sure everyone at Buddies must be very nervous to be in front of you for 3 minutes instead of one-on-one.
But I'm looking forward to getting on the phone with you.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm so glad you're here.
I'm talking to you!
I'm talking to the "Boo-Boo"!
Hello, I'm Tomiyama from Buddy's, the Power Lord of the Sakura Shake.
Yes, I'm Buddy's Name-Nee from Fukuoka.This is Buddy's Name Nee from Fukuoka Prefecture.
Kanemi-chan, Mi-chan, and Memichan... we're all eight of us.
I'm a little nervous. I'm totally nervous.
Are you all 19 years old, or are you 19, or are you students?
I love cherry blossom beds.
My sister originally liked Zelkova, so I started liking them when they came out in 2017.
I've been in love with Sakuradoko ever since then... but there's something I want to do over again...
Yes, I do.
What do you want to redo?
I cut off my hair.
Is that really okay to ask?
I'm sure there's a lot going on.
Even the circumstances. I don't know what they are.
I don't know what it's like.
Here.
I like this heart.
The heart. It's broken.
Well, it's possible.
I wonder if it's still possible these days.
Maybe it's possible if you want to have a heart to heart, but I'll ask him.
Why did you decide to cut off your hair?
I've admired your hair for 4 years since I was in high school, and I spent a lot of money on treatment and care.
But right before the Saab tour, I decided to cut off about 6 inches of my hair.
I know what you mean... women definitely do that, but...
I think it looks good on you, but I'd say go for it.
I don't know how long or how short it would be, but...
I had it down to my chest, but I cut it down to about 6 inches.
It's not 15 centimeters, is it?
Wow, so it looks completely different now.
But you kept growing it for 4 years, right?
Did you feel like it was a waste?
No, I did think it was a waste.
I'm a moody person, so I cut it off as soon as it became too painful.
I'm like you, Kurijan... if I'm in the mood and I feel like cutting it off, I do it.
And the next day I'd say I regretted it and wonder why I cut it off.
And then the next day I'd tell her how much I regretted it, and I'd tell her I'd never cut it again, and then about two days later she'd come back and tell me why she cut it.And then about two days after you say you'll never cut it again, you come back and tell me you'll never cut it again.
And there's more from there. But nowadays I don't even care about my hair anymore, so I don't. But I understand.
That's how it was a year or two ago. What about you, Honno?
I sometimes get cut off.
That's right. You get cut off?
I feel sorry for you.
I've been growing my hair long for two years, but it's always been this length.
I don't know...
I color my hair and iron it every day, so my hair gets damaged a lot.
So the hairdresser would cut the ends of my hair, or cut the parts that are a little damaged, but it's hard to grow it out if I do that every time.
I don't want her to cut my hair, I want it to grow, but I have to tell her that I can't cut it because I'm an idol.
That's right, Mame-chan.
So, when did it come to about 15 centimeters?
April... 20... what do you want to be?
I don't remember what I wanted to be, but I cut it off in late April.
I got your email.
So your sister told me about Sakurazaka. What did she mean when she talked about the costumes?
When we went on tour, my sister made me a frictionless costume as a surprise.
But I didn't tell her I'd cut my hair, and I couldn't be her, so I decided not to go.
So the outfits were ready, but... yes, they were ready, but I couldn't go.
How did you tell her?
She was...
She got angry.
But... she was making it for her.
I'm sure she'd have liked it if I'd told her sooner, but even so, she didn't mind at all.
I can be what I want to be now, right?
I'm going to go back to the way I was a few seconds ago.
I'm not saying that I wanted to wear the outfit my sister made for me...
I mean... it's fate that the costume would come at this time... after stretching it out for four years...
She said it wouldn't come for a long time. The costume got cut off.
But I'm glad there's something Douten-chan can tell you right now.
But I'm so happy that she's letting her hair grow long since it's said that hair is a woman's life.
I've been happy about that for 4 years.
But if you want to cut it, I think you should come here.
I can't stop it. That's how it is with impulses.
So you didn't do anything wrong.That means you didn't do anything wrong, Mimi.
And time will tell, and this will grow on its own. God doesn't have to do anything to make it grow, from my point of view, and you have that friction-case outfit that your sister made for you.
You have that friction case outfit your sister made for you, don't you?
I'll ask her about it.
I'll ask her. I might be able to pull it off.
I'm glad you took the trouble to make it.
I'm so happy about this episode... but from our point of view, there's nothing but love... because we're so happy...
And maybe she's not there anymore, but if she still has sadness in her heart, then she's going to have to pull up her sleeves and make a decision about Memi-chan's future.
And if you can go to a concert in Sakurazaka in the future...
I want you to come.
I'll definitely look for her. I want to see her so bad.
You want to see it? Yes, Memi-chan. I'll come.
That's so cute! That's so nice of you. Thank you.
I'm sure everyone at Buddies who's watching and listening will look at me sideways and say, "Hey, what's that?
That was on the Sakurazaka Channel. You could be Memi-chan? She's cute.
I might be, but that's okay too.
Memi-chan!
I know this is the last time I'm going to call you, but I've got Heten-chan, Hono-chan and Karin-chan here, so if there's anything you want to tell them directly...
If there's anything you want to tell me in person, or if you're in Asia, please don't hesitate to call me.
Thank you very much for giving me a lot of happiness each and every time.
Sakurazaka has become an indispensable part of my life.
I know there are many things that are painful, sad, and hard for you, but
I will stand by Sakurazaka46 no matter what.
Thank you so much for choosing to be an idol!
I will continue to support you forever and ever.
I love you so much!
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much!
I'm so happy.
Nice words.
Yeah.
Good luck with your hair.
Yes, ma'am.
Mimi!
Hi, Tami.
Oh, yes.Uh, yes.
Thank you.
I was just saying.
Now that.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
You know, I don't think I'll ever be able to say how your sister feels about you, but you're a sweet girl, Memi.
I wonder if your sister made one for herself.
I know you're not a craftsman, but still...
every time they do it... and each doll is different... right?
I wonder how they do it. It takes time.
I'm looking forward to it.
We got a lot of messages, too.
Takuman-san, if I could go back, I'd like to go back here I'd like to go back to kindergarten and stop swimming, which I've been learning since then
If not, I took swimming lessons from kindergarten to early elementary school, and because of that, the water paddle between my index finger and middle finger got really big.
It's so big!
It's amazing!
Like a kappa!
That's amazing!
It's definitely from swimming!
I can't get the ring to go all the way to the base of my finger because of it.
It's like it's stuck in there.
It makes my fingers look shorter.
It's a little hard to play the piano.
First of all, you call a human child a swimmer... well, I've never heard it called that before... but...
I think you should learn to play with water... and that's all Kit... you should waterboard each other.
It's okay to make fun of it... that's how we evolved.
But when we had to seek for food, we had to use our hands... and that's where we were headed.
If we keep on watering our hands, then, yes, 150 years from now, we'll all have index fingers popping out of our forefingers like this.
So we can survive the rain...
You're right.
What was that just now?
What?
Boo-hoo! Good luck!Boo-boo. Good luck.
Let's go.
Hello, this is Tomiyama from More Buddies.
I'm Tamura, Sakura Tako 46, this is 10 Shirin, Yamazaki. May I know your name?
May I know your name? My name is Basil.
I'm 25 years old and I'd like to ask you a favor.
What do you do for a living, Mr. Basil?
How are you doing?
When did you start liking Sakurazaka?
Before Corona became popular.
I've been a fan of Sakurazaka for about four years now... and this new song is the start of a fresh start for me.
May I start by asking what you want to redo, Basil?
I want to get back together with Buddy, who I crossed paths with two years ago.
I'd like to get back together with Buddy's, whom I crossed paths with two years ago...
He is 10 years older than me.
We got to know each other through sns, and we got to know each other better and better, and we went to our first concert together in Osaka on our first tour. I got to go to the Osaka show of the first Sakurazaka tour with this person.
After the Osaka show, we went sightseeing together.
We are good friends!
How nice!
That's so nice!
I'm so happy!
I was able to ask him to answer some questions about the area since he was from Osaka.
And on the last day of the event, the person who performed the day before was a bit...
I felt that the people who had attended the live concert the day before had a slightly different face, or rather, a slightly different atmosphere.
So that day, we ended up saying bye-bye in a rather casual way.
But we talked a little afterwards, and I found out later that he happened to be a little sick.
And I asked him to tell me that too.
I was communicating with him afterwards.
I was communicating with another Buddy's at the time, and we were getting to know each other better and better.
As the days went by, I gradually lost contact with the buddy in Osaka.
It's been two years now.
It's been two years since then.
He used to tweet a lot about the writer's work on the hill, but I knew him, and then he just disappeared.
I wonder if it was my fault or not.
Well, I...Well, I...
I've been a little slow on the uptake, and I've heard that this project is starting over, so I thought...
I thought this might be a good opportunity for us to do something, so I decided to apply.
So you haven't been in touch with him at all? That's right.
But I'm sure the older Buddy's on the other side has thought about it a few times.
I'm sure he's thought about it a few times... and I wonder if he's done so.
What do you think, Moto-chan?
It's hard to say, but I can tell you one thing, Basil, you don't have to worry about it being your fault at all.
I wonder... I wonder...
I wonder...
But I think it's kind of sweet that you're still so concerned about it.
I'm so glad that you two Buddies are getting along so well together.
I'm so glad to hear that you still care about the Buddies.
I hope we can talk again, and I hope we can see the Sakurazaka concert together.
That's the way I ended it.
I'd like to contact him and ask if he'd still be interested in going with me.
If you still want to go with me, I'd be happy to go with you.
I'd like to go to Sakurazaka live again with you.
I'd like to get to know you better.
I think it's a great opportunity for me to do something with you.
I'd like to take this opportunity to do something with you.
I think they would be very happy if I told them that there is someone who wants to go with me so much.
What do you think?
I've heard that there's a high probability that your older buddies are already looking at this.
I'd love for you to take a look at it.
I'm not sure if it's Buddy's or not.
Yes, I'm sure he's Buddy's.
What do you think, Karin?
For example...
I'd like to tell her how I'm feeling right now. I'm sure you understand, and I'm sure it's you, and I'm sure you'll understand, and I'm sure you'll understand, and I hope she comes back.
And even if he doesn't come back, since you've already said it here, maybe the embarrassment will go away.
I'm sure it'll make you feel better.
Then, I think it's a good idea to tell her that you'll be the one to get on the line.
I think that's a good strategy.
I'll tell him now.
I'm sure you'll listen to me.I'm sure you'll listen to me.
I wish I could.
I'll be there in my own time.
I'm really sorry that I haven't been in touch with you in the past two years.
I'd like to take this opportunity to contact you again.
If it's all right with you, I'd like to re-contact you and say we can have the same kind of relationship again.
If it's all right with you, I'd like to reestablish our relationship.
Yes, I will contact you.
I'll be in touch.
It's really nice.
Is there a particular song you'd like to sing with him?
I've been going to karaoke with him.
He's been a fan for quite a long time.
We are good friends.
What song is a good friend or a memorable song?
Um...
W Keyakizaka's song
Oh!
That's a song, isn't it?
I was in a karaoke class with them.
I want to see it.
Yes, I want to see it.
I'd like to see that.
I'll see you later.
I'd like to sing again when I can listen to it.
So that you can sing again?
Yes, you can.
Hey!
Thank you very much. Then, please walk to the right on Carberry together. Then we can meet up on the way or something...?
Talk about a music video! We're all ready to join you now.
Lastly, the three members of Sakurazaka are here now, and I would like to say something to Rin-chan, Hono-chan, and Kanin-chan.
You always give me so much energy. Thank you so much.
I really, really support you. I really love you. Thank you very much.
Well, we'll be praying for you.
Thank you very much.
Good luck!Come on!!!
I'll do my best!
I haven't been able to introduce many messages.
I'd like to hear them.
Let's see, a 26-year-old male from Tokushima Prefecture, buddy's name, Suit Spider Taka.
I thought I would make you laugh at the chestnut with Ten-chan, so I put on a suit and a Spiderman mask and got bored...
I was bored in my suit and Spiderman mask, and I thought it would make Tenchan laugh.
I'm sure it's true, but I'm not sure how I feel about it.
I'm sure it's true... but it's like suddenly I'm Spider-Man.
I'm going to be here all of a sudden.
You want me to be happy.
I remember how the real hawk was there just before and how he made you feel again.
That's funny. Thank you very much.
18 year old male from Saitama, Japan, buddy's name is Wahawa Ode-chan.
When I told Habu-chan at Mini-Guri that I wanted an older brother like Habu-chan, he laughed at me and said, "Not an older sister.
I was so embarrassed that I didn't know what I was talking about, and I really want to start over.
Habu-sensei is very kind, isn't he?
But from our point of view, he's very kind... and we often say to him... that he's really cool... even among the members...
Or he's my girl.
So that's what we thought.
He eats jam, he's so cool!
and then we're off to a good start, hubby...
The chorus, right? But the middle one, too...
Kosaka's in the middle... probably first, Karin...
Really, Hon-chan, that's the center line... and you're right...
But if it's just the first part, then it's just me, right?
I feel like I've been free.
I like it.
The moon is going around, and the moon is waiting around the earth.
I'm waiting for the moon to go around the earth, too.
I'm also waiting for the moon to go around the earth... and it's a little bit pink... unexpectedly pink... and I'm holding it... and I'm the best among all of them.
I'm good at that.
Fattis, you can speak English!
I'm a hedge... well, actually...
Fine 10th grade.
Fine tenth grade.s
I'm going to be here for a long time. It's so true, I'm going to be here for a long time.
You've been talking a lot, and you've been delivering.
I'm sorry, but we're done here.
What was the first one?
And then we talked about Kirikiri.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
We were having a lot of fun... and then...
But then it went on and on and on and on and on...
I was called here.
I feel a sense of responsibility, and I accept that it was a heavy responsibility.
I also felt that, as we talked on the phone, you didn't deliver the words that I had prepared, but rather, the words that I really thought on the spot.
I really felt that he was delivering what he really thought on the spot, not what he had prepared after the phone call.
I think it was a great time.
But it was very precious, and it's not often that you get to hear directly from Buddies like that, so I was very happy.
I was genuinely happy to hear that.
When is the sequel coming?
I'm glad you said you'd make a promise.
I'd like to talk to you again.
We can't sing the whole start, that's for sure.
What about you, Karin?
I don't know what's going on, but my heart is really racing right now.
I'm the complete opposite of you, but you've got that going on, and I even want to be you.
I was so surprised.
I was surprised at how much she talked to me, and I was even surprised at how much she talked to me.
Well, I hope we can do this kind of thing again.
I'd like to do this kind of episode again... well, I do want Ten-chan to be here, but she's a must.
I'm not that tall, so go ahead and do it, I'm really scared.
I think it's the three of us in the top two, but I think we've got the right balance of aggressiveness and momentum, and Ten, who's careful and deliberate, and Rin, who's deep in her thoughts, and we've got to balance that out and make sure that it's balanced.
You're thinking, "If it goes too far this way, or I have to go this way now," aren't you?
Yes, I may have been worrying about that every day.
Yes, sir.
I'm looking forward to it.
Sakurazaka is going to perform at the Japan Expo Parry 2023 in France.
I'm sure you know there are a lot of overseas fans, but what do you think?
I'm very happy to be able to go and see all my buddies overseas, and I'm really looking forward to seeing you all.First of all, I'm really happy to be able to go see my buddies overseas, and I've been saying for a long time that I'm going to do my best to go see them.
I've been saying I'd do my best to go see them, and I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to it, but it's my first time abroad.
I'm looking forward to it, but it's my first time abroad.
I wish they'd make it into an arsh!
What's so great about it?
I did all the mold and makeup myself...
I mean, the photographer took a picture of me with my right shoulder down, chin down, smiling and taking a quick picture, but it looks like I'm leaking so much!
It's better to take it at the passport office.
Well, but you can't see it somewhere, can you?
Sakurazaka-chan might be subliminally shown for about 0.00001 seconds in the video that's playing today.
There's still a possibility that it will be shown in some scene.
It may not play for 0.00001 seconds, but it's important that you watch it over and over again without bears.
I'd like to leave you all with the hope that it may happen again.
If you enjoyed today's episode, please give us a high rating and subscribe to our channel.
Subscribe to our channel for sure!
Tei-chan, one last thing.
Me?
Oh, no!
That's not good!
That's scary.
I've never seen anything like it.
ohohoh?
ohohoh...
Cut it, please.
Bye-bye!
Subscribe to our channel, please.
undefined